<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?><zebradogs>	<zdog		name="ALYSSA KOHLER"		bioimage="alyssa.jpg"		par1="You think you have it rough? Try living in a green and gold state when your favorite color is purple. Having to sit quietly while everyone talks about the Packers’ 12 league championships and three Super Bowl victories—this when your team is pitching an oh-fer in the big one? Ouch. Even worse, having to live with the memory of the 1998 season? You know, that year the Vikes went 15-1, were easily the best team in the NFL, and Gary Anderson misses that field goal in the NFC championship game? The same Gary Anderson who hadn’t missed all year prior to that? That’s more burden than anyone should have to shoulder. We feel for Alyssa. That’s why we never tell anyone she’s a Vikings fan. Ever. Shhh."		par2=""		par3=""		par4=""		par5=""		par6=""		par7=""		par8=""		par9=""		email="alyssa@zebradog.com"	/>	<zdog		name="AMANDA BERG"		bioimage="amanda.jpg"		par1="Coming Soon"		par2=""		par3=""		par4=""		par5=""		par6=""		par7=""		par8=""		par9=""		email="geoff@zebradog.com"	/>	<zdog		name="AMY BEYLER"		bioimage="amy.jpg"		par1="Imagine a flawless life in Anytown, USA. Can you see the picket fence? How about that perfect husband, the two wonderful children and a third one on the way? The best house on the block and the most meticulously manicured lawn? It's all Cleaverville and that's our girl Amy Beyler. But there's a dirty little secret you may not know. It's a doozey too. On the highest shelf in the darkest closet in the last box behind all the junkiest junk, there are pictures. Lots and lots of pictures. Amy backstage in her ripped jeans, concert tee, cigarette dangling, bangs teased to the heavens, devil fingers and acting all scowly standing next to . . . Poison. Yes, that Poison. The 'I Want Action Tonight' Poison. Brett Michaels, C.C, and the rest of the crew Poison.  Well look what the cat dragged in mom, and don't tell the neighborhood. And the best part is, she wanted to be there. So if you're still wondering just what exactly an Unskinny Bop is, you go ahead and ask her. She'll tell you."		par2=""		par3=""		par4=""		par5=""		par6=""		par7=""		par8=""		par9=""		email="amy@zebradog.com"	/>	<zdog		name="CANDICE NIELSEN"		bioimage="candice.jpg"		par1="BORN: Candice with an “i”, just like Candice Bergmann, the actress, though no acting talents to speak of." 			par2="CHILDHOOD: Went by the alias “Candi”, officially retired name at high school graduation. Still have my collection of scented Strawberry Shortcake figurines (they still smell)."		par3="TEEN YEARS: Played every sport under the sun. Homecoming queen. Cheesy hair."		par4="COLLEGE YEARS: Poor, art student. Graduate of UW-Madison. Lived on W. Washington in Madison. Financed  education working as a waitress at the Madison Club."		par5="FIRST JOB: Scooped ice cream. I can artifully scoop a darn good cone. First real job: public relations."		par6="MARRIED: Lars-Oluf Nielsen, a crazy Dane and former Royal Guard. Married in a castle in Denmark, the country. No kiddin’."		par7="KIDS: Anna. 2+ years. A handful and tons of fun."		par8="CREDO: Work Hard. Play Hard. Be Kind. Have Fun."		par9="FOR FUN: Love to cook. Hang out with friends and family. Volunteer. Workout. Someday, I will run a marathon."		email="candice@zebradog.com"	/>	<zdog		name="CHRISTOPHER MOORE"		bioimage="chris.jpg"		par1="A love story. Old wine in a new bottle, but still. In college, boy meets girl. Her name: 1979 Yamaha 250 single-cylinder. She’s beautiful. Predictably, boy falls in love. Boy neglects to buy license. Doesn’t care. Love. Girl is stolen away by bad men. Boy is heartbroken, but moves on. Years pass. Boy turns to man. Man finds new love. Her name: Janine. Storybook. One day, serendipity. Yamaha is found. Feelings flood. New girl understands, kind of. Raises eyebrow. Says, Chris? Man is torn, but not dumb. Man trades (trades!) Yamaha for 1974 Wurlitzer Electric Piano. He doesn’t play the piano. At all. Not because he doesn’t want to, because he doesn’t know how. Janine is happy. Man is . . . happy. Somewhere: Fonda, Hopper, and Nicholson weep."		par2=""		par3=""		par4=""		par5=""		par6=""		par7=""		par8=""		par9=""		email="alyssa@zebradog.com"	/>	<zdog		name="DEVON HOFMAN-SCHRIEBER"		bioimage="devon.jpg"		par1="Well, I don't know, you don't plan this stuff, this was Horicon back in the 80s and I guess it started when I was trying to copy my dad's drawings and paintings from the attic, but see, there's these detours, like the, oh my God, big frizzy hair tight rolled jeans New Kids on the Block Vanilla Ice fiascos. You get through that stuff, somehow, we all do but do you find the art then? No, of course not, this is when you get into working at a salon and your hair goes, like, crazy and one day it's long and brown and then the next, black and pink and then black and red and then for some unknown reason you land on platinum white. Okay, that's fine, but the retail thing? Where did that come from? I don't know what I was thinking, but I'll tell you what you get eight years later, you get a bad shopping habit a huge closet and not one thing to wear. So then it's almost twenty years after the attic and I finally get back to that art thing and finish school and that's cool and great because this is where I'm supposed to be. But you know what the thing is? Yeah, that's right, I still don't have anything to wear."		par2=""		par3=""		par4=""		par5=""		par6=""		par7=""		par8=""		par9=""		email="devon@zebradog.com"	/>	<zdog		name="EVAN SCHULTZ"		bioimage="evan.jpg"		par1="If you're Evan Schultz, this is how you end up as first-rate web and Flash guru at ZD Studios: First you're born in the artistic hotbed of Wausau, WI. Then, when you're five, move to an 80-acre cattle ranch in Merrill and nurture your creativity looking at cows. Realize ranching is not your destiny while at the same time honing your vegetarian leanings. Later, move to the big city and go to UW-Madison and take lots of calc and physics so you can major in computer science. Decide you don't really like that and switch to landscape architecture. Again change your mind as you realize planning shrub locations and land use patterns isn't so much fun either. Settle on art. Graduate. You are happy. Move to Boulder, find your inner granola and save prairie dogs by pulling them out of their holes and relocating them. After nine years, relocate your own self back to Madison. Buy a leather Packers jacket with an enormous G on the back. Wear it often."		par2=""		par3=""		par4=""		par5=""		par6=""		par7=""		par8=""		par9=""		email="evan@zebradog.com"	/>	<zdog		name="GEOFF SABIN"		bioimage="geoff.jpg"		par1="I'm still thinking about who I am, and what I've done for the world."		par2=""		par3=""		par4=""		par5=""		par6=""		par7=""		par8=""		par9=""		email="geoff@zebradog.com"	/>	<zdog		name="GRETA SECKMAN"		bioimage="greta.jpg"		par1="Greta is mysterious. Very mysterious."		par2=""		par3=""		par4=""		par5=""		par6=""		par7=""		par8=""		par9=""		email="greta@zebradog.com"	/>	<zdog		name="JULIE SCHMITZ"		bioimage="julie.jpg"		par1="Julie comes to us from the far reaches of the Norwegian village of Austafjord. She skied here as a little girl to study Journalism and Psychology at the University of Wisconsin. Julie learned the English language so well she now sounds like a girl from Brookfield Wisconsin. After a successful career owning and operating a gourmet catering business, Julie decided to try a psychological experiment involving the birth of twins and a blonde superstar. She has been generally successful and has learned a great deal of patience and humor."		par2="Julie has just completed her third Marathon in 18 months. She continues to run but we do not know where she is running to. Possibly away from her experiment but most likely not. She is in charge of the Gun and the Checkbook at ZD Studios."		par3="We will continue to monitor her experiments with running and childbirth as we look forward to the Norwegian Caterer children's book series soon to hit a Borders near you."		par4=""		par5=""		par6=""		par7=""		par8=""		par9=""		email="julie@zebradog.com"	/>	<zdog		name="KRIS MARCONNET"		bioimage="kris.jpg"		par1="Our lovely Kris is a testament to the death of the housewife. Don’t worry, she’s as healthy as a tulip in springtime. What we’re talking about is the dissolution of a construct—the whole I’ll vacuum the living room and then take an hour off to watch General Hospital before baking cookies, paradigm. No, for seven years Kris was a full-time mother/freelancer. That means on her best days her two girls were only screaming in the background (as girls are wont to do), and on her more trying days you could find her darlings hanging from her elbows as she applied a Gaussian blur. So what of reentering the rough and tumble ad world where the word mother is most often followed by a two-syllable expletive? Eh, she says and yawns, piece of mother freaking cake."		par2=""		par3=""		par4=""		par5=""		par6=""		par7=""		par8=""		par9=""		email="kris@zebradog.com"	/>	<zdog		name="LOUIS COLESCOTT"		bioimage="louis.jpg"		par1="If there's such a thing as kismet, as a true destiny, it has to be the life of Louis Colescott. Born the son of an artist and printmaker right here in Madison, Louis has always had more than a little ink in his blood. But being an artist in every way, and always preferring the non-linear, it just took him some time and more than a few zigzags to get back here. Starting out at the, gasp, U. of Minnesota, Louis crisscrossed the states from art school in LA to a high-profile job in NYC before the pastoral pull of the Midwest dragged him back. Trading in his subway pass for a not-so-trusty Volvo wagon and a picturesque hour commute from Baraboo, LC couldn't be happier. So Happy Hill is where you'll find him now, and happy too is the Colescott brood which now includes: one wife, two kids, one dog, three cats and a kick-ass donkey named Chester."		par2=""		par3=""		par4=""		par5=""		par6=""		par7=""		par8=""		par9=""		email="louis@zebradog.com"	/>	<zdog		name="MARK SCHMITZ" 		bioimage="mark.jpg" 		par1="BORN: Mark William Schmitz during The Kennedy Administration. 4 cents for a stamp. Bald"		par2="CHILDHOOD: Happy, artistic. Loved my Stingray. (Blue metallic, white banana seat, sissy bar) Bart Starr football card pinned to the back tire. First artistic memory: learning how to finger paint a peace sign. Blonde curly hair."		par3="TEEN YEARS: Clogs, shark tooth necklace, peace sign T shirt. Tennis and bump skiing were my passions until I met Stacy Droster. Starsky & Hutch afro."		par4="COLLEGE YEARS:  Art student. Never went to class. Wore 80's clothes and danced to 'Fers'. Lived on State Street in Madison. 80's afro/mullett."		par5="FIRST JOB: Denver Colorado. Lived in Boulder. Skied like a wild man. Fell in love. Corporate afro."		par6="MARRIED: Julie Anderson. Worked for ad agencies while learning to fly fish. Corporate curly."		par7="KIDS: Riley + Twins Greta and Cole. Changed everything forever. Gray fading curly."		par8="CAREER: Started ZD Studios in 1994. Passion and Business meet. Propecia."		par9="CREDO: Comb your hair, brush your teeth, never lie, work hard... all will be fine."		email="mark@zebradog.com"	/>	<zdog		name="MATT TEDORE"		bioimage="matt.jpg"		par1="Matt's a Renaissance Man. One of those guys who's always pushing what's possible and going a million miles an hour. You name an ing, he does it: kayaking, biking, gaming, camping, painting, illustrating . . .and that's not to mention the myriad other interests we don't have time for here. And the thing is, all of it's pursued with his trademark vigor and verve. He's not only shifting the paradigm, he's actually blowing that thing right out of the water and reassembling the pieces into his own personal art project. One can't help but wonder if Matt's stretched the possibilities so far that he's actually evolving into a new type of being. We suspect this to be true because Matt has six toes on his left foot. Not five toes and a nubbin, not five toes with a bunion or a wart, but a straight-up extra toe. Count them: One, two, three, four, five six. Seriously." 		par2="Freak."		par3=""		par4=""		par5=""		par6=""		par7=""		par8=""		par9=""		email="matt@zebradog.com"	/>	<zdog		name="MELANIE KRANZ"		bioimage="melanie.jpg"		par1="If you've worked with ZD, you know Melanie. In fact, if you don't work with ZD, chances are you still know Mel. Between being a life-long Madisonian, an aerobics instructor, the nine years bartending at Hatters, and the hundreds of football and basketball games, she knows everyone. Rumor has it that she worked at ZD before the Jackman building was even built, but we can't confirm that. So you think you know Mel? Let's just see how smart you really are."		par2="1. Melanie's favorite color is: A. Pink B. Blue C. Mike Wilkenson, Forward, UW Badgers"		par3="2. Melanie has dated: A. A male ballerina B. A guy who roasts pigs for a living (nickname: Mr. Picnic) C. A pasta chef D. An actuary E. A race car driver F. Rod Ripley, Forward, UW Badgers G. All of the above"		par4="3. Melanie's favorite thing for lunch is: A. Anything from the Oakcrest Tavern B. Nothing. Working within walking distance of 150 restaurants makes no difference. It's all gross if it's not the Oakcrest. C. Both A and B."		par5="4. Melanie once had framed pictures of Matthew Perry (Chandler from Friends) on her desk: A. True B. False"		par6="5. Mel bartended at Madhatters for nine years. Why? A. Because she thought it would be good to have a second job for every year she was still in college. B. She wanted to work there one year for every time she was a bridesmaid. C. It's a good place to meet forwards from the UW hoops team."		par7="6. What kind of music does Mel listen to? A. Varsity B. Anything she can dance to. C. Bud song D.Body Pump Body Rock Volumes 1 ­ 27"		par8="7. The only thing farther away from the court in the Kohl Center than Melanie's season tickets in Section 317 are: A. The Nitty Gritty B. Jupiter C. Nothing. Absolutely nothing."		par9="8. If Mel could have any job in the world, what would it be? A. Dancer B. Cook at the Oakcrest C. Forward, UW Badgers"		email="melanie@zebradog.com"	/>	<zdog		name="MIKE KOVATCH"		bioimage="mike.jpg"		par1="The peripatetic, coastally ambidextrous Mike Kovatch is living the dream. A lifelong sports fan, he’s designed trading cards professionally. A diehard Notre Dame nut, he’s appeared in the movie Rudy. A notorious prankster, he’s played a practical joke that set up his best friend and future wife. But in light of all this sunshine, we can’t help but wonder if our well-traveled Mike didn’t at some point make a Robert Johnson-esque deal at the crossroads. We ask not because his soul seems particularly tortured; to the contrary he’s actually quite pleasant. Rather, since his suitcase landed in Wisconsin, we’ve learned he hates cheese. Doesn’t like it even a little bit. Logic then suggests it can only be the devil—either that or karmic penance for the whole Notre Dame thing."		par2=""		par3=""		par4=""		par5=""		par6=""		par7=""		par8=""		par9=""		email="mike@zebradog.com"	/>	<zdog		name="RASHEID ATLAS"		bioimage="rasheid.jpg"		par1="Rasheid Atlas has by far the coolest name at ZD Studios. Actually, he has pretty much the coolest name we've ever heard. It's the kind of made-up name that's usually reserved for professional wrestlers, stand-up comedians and porn stars. While he most certainly is big, funny and sexy, he insists he's never held any of those jobs. We have no reason not to believe him."		par2=""		par3=""		par4=""		par5=""		par6=""		par7=""		par8=""		par9=""		email="rasheid@zebradog.com"	/>	<zdog		name="ROSS CATTELAN"		bioimage="ross.jpg"		par1="Born in Denmark (the city near Green Bay, not the country) in 1972, Ross Cattelan never quite fit the northern Wisconsin mold. Always preferring his colored pencils and paints to rifles and NASCAR, he eventually found himself at ZD Studios. After a four-year stint, and needing even more culture than Madison could provide, he packed up his stuff and headed west to settle in the bohemian mecca of Portland. Not coincidentally, it's also the strip club capital of the world. Ever on the move, these days he heads up the ZD satellite office in Seattle. He spends his days biking, snowboarding, getting married at Moab and getting out of the way of his wife's (and now begrudgingly his) deaf and blind dogs, Dylan and Cooper."		par2=""		par3=""		par4=""		par5=""		par6=""		par7=""		par8=""		par9=""		email="ross@zebradog.com"	/></zebradogs>